HERE Organizing Department Files on Microfilm 6199/003 mf
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
HERE Organizing Department Files on Microfilm
1919-1994
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Hotel Employees and Restaurant Employees International Union (HERE)
6199/003 mf
8.17 cubic feet
70 microfilm reels
Records, microfilm.
8254403
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, June 03, 2014
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, August 21, 2015
Scope and Contents
This collection is made up of the following: Director of Organization Miscellaneous Files 1983-1991; Organization Department Miscellaneous Files; Organizer Wkly Report Forms 1989-1990; L.S.O. 1977-1980 [Locals 10, 116, 634]; Organizer files Int'l. L.S.O. files; W.R.O. Org. Files; E.R.O files; L.S.O. Financial Assistance files 1985-1989.
Some negative copies available upon request.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: All 6199 Collectins
Hotel Employees and Restaurant Employees International Union; Hotel Employees and Restaurant Employees International Union. Local 40
8254403
- D.O. Misc. - B/S Chas Neg. 1987-82 -- 1983-84 Hilton, Atlanta Master (Reel 1)
  - B/S Chas. Negotiations, 1976-1982; 1 (Reel 1)
  - 1981 Beefsteak Charlie's Negotiation, 2 (Reel 1)
  - 1982 Beefsteak Charlie's Negotiation, 3 (Reel 1)
  - 1973-75 Host International, 1973-1975; 4 (Reel 1)
  - Union Busting Material, 1979-1981; 5 (Reel 1)
  - Union Buster Seminar June 1980 - April 14, 1980 - March 16, 1981, 1980-1981; 6 (Reel 1)
  - Hyatt Corporation, 1981-1982; 7 (Reel 1)
  - Host International 1981-82 Survey of Contract, 1981-1982; 8 (Reel 1)
  - Organizing Seminar Las Vegas (March 15-19, 1982), 9 (Reel 1)
  - AFL-CIO Cooperative Organizing Campaign Indiana, 1982; 10 (Reel 1)
  - 1981 Convention, 11 (Reel 1)
  - AFL-CIO Cooperative Organizing Campaign Indiana, 12 (Reel 1)
  - AFL-CIO Arkansas-Oklahoma Co-Op, 1983; 13 (Reel 1)
  - Hilton 1981-1982, 14 (Reel 1)
  - 1983-84 Hilton, Atlanta Airport, 1983-1984; 15 (Reel 1)
- D.O. Misc. - Org. Campaign Ind. '83 -- '61-'84 NLRB Elect. Master (Reel 2)
  - AFL-CIO Cooperative Organizing Campaign Indiana, 1983, 1 (Reel 2)
  - 1983 AFL-CIO National Organizing Coordinating Committee Rub Sheets, 2 (Reel 2)
  - 1983 Beefsteak Charlie's Nego., 3 (Reel 2)
  - Cooperative Angel Network "Can" 1983-85, 1983-1985; 4 (Reel 2)
  - 1983 Holiday Inn, 5 (Reel 2)
  - Hotel Survey of Local Unions, 1982-1983; 6 (Reel 2)
  - 1983 Hyatt, 7 (Reel 2)
  - 1981 Hyatt Survey, 8 (Reel 2)
  - 1983 Host International, 9 (Reel 2)
  - 1982 INHILCO Contract-Effective, 1980-1983; 10 (Reel 2)
  - 1980-1986 INHILCO Miscellaneous Correspondence, 11 (Reel 2)
  - Pension Plan - International, 1982; 12 (Reel 2)
  - 1983 Servomation Corporation, 13 (Reel 2)
  - W.E.S.T. 1983 Washington Employees on Service Trades Proposition 312, 14 (Reel 2)
  - W.E.S.T. Proposition 312 Picket Expenses and Per Capita Tax, 15 (Reel 2)
  - AFL-CIO Cooperative Organizing Campaign Indiana, 1984; 16 (Reel 2)
  - AFL-CIO Arkansas-Oklahoma Cooperative Organizing, 1984; 17 (Reel 2)
  - AFL-CIO Cooperative Organizing Campaign Indiana, 1985; 18 (Reel 2)
  - AFL-CIO National Organizing Coordinating Committee Rub Sheets, 1984; 19 (Reel 2)
  - 1984 Beefsteak Charlie's Negotiation, 20 (Reel 2)
  - 1984-88 Circus Circus - Reno H+W Re-Open/Arbitration, 1984-1988; 21 (Reel 2)
  - Hilton Hotels 1984, 22 (Reel 2)
  - Holiday Inn 1984, 23 (Reel 2)
  - 1984 IUF/ILO, 24 (Reel 2)
  - 1961-84 NLRB Elections, 1961-1984; 25 (Reel 2)
- D.O. Misc. -- Ogden Food '76-'84 -- '85 L A Org. Comm (Reel 3)
  - 12/76 - 7/84 Ogden Food, 1976-1984; 1 (Reel 3)
  - Sambos 1984, 2 (Reel 3)
  - 1984 Local 2, San Francisco SCOMA Negotiations/Strike, 3 (Reel 3)
  - 1984 Servomation Corporation, 4 (Reel 3)
  - 1984 Union Busting Index, 5 (Reel 3)
  - 1984 W.E.S.T. Washington Employees in Service Trade, 6 (Reel 3)
  - Yale 1984, 7 (Reel 3)
  - American Institute for Free Labor Development, 1985; 8 (Reel 3)
  - ARA Vending Service, 1985; 9 (Reel 3)
  - AFL-CIO IUD Industrial Union Department, 1985; 10 (Reel 3)
  - AFL-CIO National Organizing Committee, 1985; 11 (Reel 3)
  - AFL-CIO National Organizing Coordinating Committee Rub Sheets, 1985; 12 (Reel 3)
  - 1985 Beefsteak Charlie's Negotiations, 13 (Reel 3)
  - 1983-85 Circus Circus/Reno H+W #152, 1983-1985; 14 (Reel 3)
  - Evolution of Work Staff Committee, 1985; 15 (Reel 3)
  - 1985 F.A.S.T. Expenses, 16 (Reel 3)
  - GEB 1985 Meeting, 17 (Reel 3)
  - Guam Report, 18 (Reel 3)
  - Hilton 1985, 19 (Reel 3)
  - Holiday Inn, 1985; 20 (Reel 3)
  - IUF Corporate Profiles, 1985; 21 (Reel 3)
  - IUF Miscellaneous, 1985; 22 (Reel 3)
  - IUF-Meetings - Miscellaneous Meetings, 1985; 23 (Reel 3)
  - IUF/NARO, 1985; 24 (Reel 3)
  - IUF-Nestle, 1985; 25 (Reel 3)
  - IUF-South Africa, 1985; 26 (Reel 3)
  - IUF Support, 1985-1987; 27 (Reel 3)
  - Holiday Inn - Glendale, CA Local 531 NLRB, 1984-1985; 28 (Reel 3)
  - Legal Services Borovsky, Ehrlich, and Kronenberg, 1985; 29 (Reel 3)
  - Los Angeles, Orange Counties Organizing Committee, 1985; 30 (Reel 3)
- D.O. Misc. '85 NLRB Elections -- Gen. Executive Bd. '86 MASTER (Reel 4)
  - NLRB Elections, 1985; 1 (Reel 4)
  - High Sierra (Sahara Tahoe) Local 86 Corporate Contract, 1981-1985; 2 (Reel 4)
  - Rainbow House Contract, 1981-1985; 3 (Reel 4)
  - Conferences - Organizing Toronto, CA, 1985; 4 (Reel 4)
  - Yale, 1985; 5 (Reel 4)
  - W.E.S.T. 1985 Washington Employees in Service Trades Proposition 312, 6 (Reel 4)
  - California Labor Federation AFL-CIO, Trade Union Summer School September 21-26, 1986, 7 (Reel 4)
  - AFL-CIO Cooperative Organizing Campaign - Indiana 1986, 8 (Reel 4)
  - AFL-CIO National Organizing Committee 1986, 9 (Reel 4)
  - AFL-CIO National Organizing Coordinating Committee Rub Sheets, 1986; 10 (Reel 4)
  - AFL-CIO Miscellaneous, 1986; 11 (Reel 4)
  - AFL-CIO Organizing Steering Committee, 1986; 12 (Reel 4)
  - AFL-CIO Task Force on Associate Membership, 1986; 13 (Reel 4)
  - American Institute for Free Labor Development, 1986; 14 (Reel 4)
  - ARA 1986, 15 (Reel 4)
  - Amtrak Workers Council, 1986; 16 (Reel 4)
  - Associate Membership Program Kamper Group, 1986; 17 (Reel 4)
  - Amtrak Petitions, 1986; 18 (Reel 4)
  - 1986 Beefsteak Charlie's Negotiation, 19 (Reel 4)
  - 1986 Beefsteak Charlie's Local 25 Arbitration, 20 (Reel 4)
  - 1986 F.A.S.T. Expenses, 21 (Reel 4)
  - Harvard Organizing Drive, 1986-1987; 22 (Reel 4)
  - General Executive Board Meeting 1986, 23 (Reel 4)
- D.O. Misc. -- 1980-86 Hosts Int'l. 1987 Assoc. Memb Prog Master (Reel 5)
  - 1980-86 Hosts International (Marriott), 1980-1986; 1 (Reel 5)
  - INHILCO-Research, 1986; 2 (Reel 5)
  - IUF-Corporate Profiles, 1986; 3 (Reel 5)
  - IUF Executive Committee April 1-5, 1986, 4 (Reel 5)
  - IUF Miscellaneous, 1986; 5 (Reel 5)
  - IUF Miscellaneous Meetings, 1986; 6 (Reel 5)
  - IUF/NARO, 1986; 7 (Reel 5)
  - IUF-Nestles, 1986; 8 (Reel 5)
  - IUF-South Africa, 1986; 9 (Reel 5)
  - IUF Support, 1986; 10 (Reel 5)
  - ILO, 1986; 11 (Reel 5)
  - Director of Organization Mailings (1/3/86 - 12/30/86), 1986; 12 (Reel 5)
  - Re: NLRB, 1986; 13 (Reel 5)
  - K. Lechow's Updates, 1986; 14 (Reel 5)
  - Ogden Mailing, 1986; 15 (Reel 5)
  - Radison Campaign, 1986; 16 (Reel 5)
  - 1986 LA Radisson Plaza Hotel Employees Handbook Medical Plan, 17 (Reel 5)
  - LA Radisson Insurance Enrollment, 1986; 18 (Reel 5)
  - Texas Triangle Organizing Committee, 1986; 19 (Reel 5)
  - Yale, 1986; 20 (Reel 5)
  - AFL-CIO Coorperative Organizing Campaign - Indiana, 1987; 21 (Reel 5)
  - AFL-CIO National Organizing Committee, 1987; 22 (Reel 5)
  - AFL-CIO Miscellaneous, 1987; 23 (Reel 5)
  - AFL-CIO National Organizing Coordinating Committee Rub Sheets, 1987; 24 (Reel 5)
  - AFL-CIO Department of Organizing Coordinating Committee Rub Sheets, 1987; 25 (Reel 5)
  - American Institute for Free Labor Development, 1987; 26 (Reel 5)
  - ARA, 1987; 27 (Reel 5)
  - Associate Membership Program - Kamper Group, 1987; 28 (Reel 5)
- D.O. Misc. - '87 AFL-CIO -- KY-OH Org. -- 1987 Mailings Master (Reel 6)
  - AFL-CIO, KY-OH Organization Campaign, 1987; 1 (Reel 6)
  - Amtrak Workers Council, 1987; 2 (Reel 6)
  - H&W - VJS Trustees Suit Re: Brock vs. Gerace, 1987; 3 (Reel 6)
  - Brock v. Gerace, 1987; 4 (Reel 6)
  - Cincinnati Convention Center Dispute Ogden Food, 1987; 5 (Reel 6)
  - Brock v. Hanley et. Al. (3/87 - 3/88), 1987-1988; 6 (Reel 6)
  - CLUW, 1986-1987; 7 (Reel 6)
  - Drug Testing, 1986-1987; 8 (Reel 6)
  - F.A.S.T. Expenses, 1987; 9 (Reel 6)
  - General Executive Board, 1987; 10 (Reel 6)
  - Julius G. Getman Interviews with Vincent J. Sirabella, 1987; 11 (Reel 6)
  - Holiday Corp./Harrah's, 1987; 12 (Reel 6)
  - Holiday Inn (Las Vegas), 1987; 13 (Reel 6)
  - Hyatt Employee Manuals, 1987; 14 (Reel 6)
  - INHILCO Contract - English and Spanish, 1986-1989; 15 (Reel 6)
  - Mailings, 1987; 16 (Reel 6)
- D.O. Misc. -- Immigration 1987-88 '87 LA Org. Comm. Master (Reel 7)
  - Immigration, 1987-1988; 1 (Reel 7)
  - IUF Corporate Profiles, 1987; 2 (Reel 7)
  - IUF Meetings Cyprus, 11/9-11/13, 1987; 3 (Reel 7)
  - IUF AC Meeting October 2-3, 1987 - Germany, 4 (Reel 7)
  - IUF/NARO, 1987; 5 (Reel 7)
  - IUF-Nestles, 1987; 6 (Reel 7)
  - IUF Miscellaneous, 1987; 7 (Reel 7)
  - IUF Meetings, January 1987, 8 (Reel 7)
  - IUF Meeting Geneva, Switzerland - March 17-19, 1987, 9 (Reel 7)
  - IUF Executive Committee Meeting April 2, 1987, 10 (Reel 7)
  - Eth. & VJS Regional Conference, 1987; 11 (Reel 7)
  - Morty Miller Updates, 1987; 12 (Reel 7)
  - George Meany - Center for Labor Studies, 1987; 13 (Reel 7)
  - NLRB Elections, 1987; 14 (Reel 7)
  - NARO/Nestle, 1987; 15 (Reel 7)
  - IUF Support, 1987; 16 (Reel 7)
  - Right to Work, 1981-1987; 17 (Reel 7)
  - IUF - South Africa, 1987; 18 (Reel 7)
  - Hyatt Hotels, 1984-1987; 19 (Reel 7)
  - K. Kechow's Updates, 1987; 20 (Reel 7)
  - Los Angeles, Orange Counties Organizing Committee, 1987; 21 (Reel 7)
- D.O. Misc. -- '87 S.F. Rest. Negot. -- Mclaughlin vs. Gerace Master (Reel 8)
  - San Francisco Rest. Negotiations, 1987; 1 (Reel 8)
  - Yale, 1987-1989; 2 (Reel 8)
  - Martin E. Segal Company, 1987-1988; 3 (Reel 8)
  - Regilious Leaders, 1987; 4 (Reel 8)
  - Texas Triangle Organizing Committee, 1987; 5 (Reel 8)
  - AFL-CIO Cooperative Organizing Campaign, 1988; 6 (Reel 8)
  - Beefsteak Charlie's 1988, 7 (Reel 8)
  - AFL-CIO National Organizing Committee 1988, 8 (Reel 8)
  - AFL-CIO Miscellaneous, 1988; 9 (Reel 8)
  - FLO-CIO Department of Organizing and Field Services, 1988; 10 (Reel 8)
  - IUD-AFL-CIO, 1988; 11 (Reel 8)
  - AFL-CIO KY-OH Organizing Campaign, 1988; 12 (Reel 8)
  - AFL-CIO National Organizing Coordinating Committee Rub Sheets, 1988; 13 (Reel 8)
  - AFL-CIO New England Organizing Committee, 1988; 14 (Reel 8)
  - AFL-CIO Task Force on Associate Membership, 1985; 15 (Reel 8)
  - AFL-CIO Executive Council Transportation Committee, 1988; 16 (Reel 8)
  - American Institute for Free Labor Development, 1988; 17 (Reel 8)
  - Amtrak Workers Council, 1988; 18 (Reel 8)
  - Boston Film, 1983-1988; 19 (Reel 8)
  - Bellevue Stratford Hotel - Hotel Atop the Bellevue Cunard Lines, 1988; 20 (Reel 8)
  - Brock v. Gerace #85-3669, 1988; 21 (Reel 8)
  - Canadian Organizing 1986-88, 1986-1988; 22 (Reel 8)
  - Chelsea Catering, 1988; 23 (Reel 8)
  - Circus Circus - Reno, 1986-1988; 24 (Reel 8)
  - College of the Desert - Palm Desert, CA, 1986-1988; 25 (Reel 8)
  - McLaughlin v. Gerace-McLaughlin v. Hanley, 1988; 26 (Reel 8)
- D.O. Misc. - '88 El Paso Hilton -- '85-88 IUF Women Iss. Master (Reel 9)
  - El Paso Hilton, 1988; 1 (Reel 9)
  - Information - El Paso Hilton, 2 (Reel 9)
  - El Paso Hilton, 1988-1991; 3 (Reel 9)
  - Greyhound Food Management - Phoenix, AZ and Tulsa, OK, 1987-1988; 4 (Reel 9)
  - IUF - Corporate Profiles, 1988; 5 (Reel 9)
  - Hyatt, 1988-1991; 6 (Reel 9)
  - ILO, 1988; 7 (Reel 9)
  - IUF - South Africa, 1988-1989; 8 (Reel 9)
  - IUF - Nestles, 1988; 9 (Reel 9)
  - IUF Support Letters, 1988; 10 (Reel 9)
  - IUF Miscellaneous, 1988; 11 (Reel 9)
  - IUF Women's Issues, 1985-1988; 12 (Reel 9)
- D.O. Misc. -- '88 Orange Co Org. Comm. -- Hotel Syracuse Negot. Master (Reel 10)
  - Los Angeles, Orange Counties Organizing Committee, 1988; 1 (Reel 10)
  - Military/Airline Survey, 2 (Reel 10)
  - Morty Miller Updates, 1988; 3 (Reel 10)
  - Montana Local, 1986-1988; 4 (Reel 10)
  - Radisson Plaza Hotel, 1988; 5 (Reel 10)
  - La Radisson Company medical Premiums, 1986-1988; 6 (Reel 10)
  - Rainbow House, 1988; 7 (Reel 10)
  - 1987-1988 Martin E. Segal Company, 8 (Reel 10)
  - NLRB Elections, 1988; 9 (Reel 10)
  - LA Radisson Union Proposal Information, 1988-1989; 10 (Reel 10)
  - Hotel Syracuse - Negotiations, 1988-1989; 11 (Reel 10)
- D.O. Misc. -- '83-88 Teamster File -- '89 Inhilco Negot. Master (Reel 11)
  - Teamster File, 1983-1988; 1 (Reel 11)
  - Texas Triangle Organizing Committee, 1988; 2 (Reel 11)
  - Union Busting Activities, 1988; 3 (Reel 11)
  - Union Industries Show - January 13, 1988, 4 (Reel 11)
  - AFL-CIO Cooperative Organizing Campaign KY-OH, 1989; 5 (Reel 11)
  - Los Angeles, Orange Counties Organizing Committee, 1989; 6 (Reel 11)
  - AFL-CIO Department Information, 1989; 7 (Reel 11)
  - B/S Chas.Wage Re-Opener, 1989; 8 (Reel 11)
  - AFL-CIO Cooperateive Organizing Campaign - IND., 1989; 9 (Reel 11)
  - AFL-CIO National Organizing Committee, 1989; 10 (Reel 11)
  - AFL-CIO Industrial Union Department, 1989; 11 (Reel 11)
  - AFL-CIO Organizing Institute, 1989; 12 (Reel 11)
  - Amtrak Workers Council, 1989; 13 (Reel 11)
  - Beefsteak Charlie's, 14 (Reel 11)
  - AFL-CIO National Organizing Coordinating Committee Rub Sheets, 1989; 15 (Reel 11)
  - B/S Chas.89 Negotiations, 1989; 16 (Reel 11)
  - Davis Cowell and Bowe Decertification Handbilling/Picketing Bankruptcy NLRB, 1983-1989; 17 (Reel 11)
  - Eastern Airlines Strike, 1989; 18 (Reel 11)
  - F.A.S.T. Expenses, 1988-1989; 19 (Reel 11)
  - Gus Genetti Hotel - Local 134, 1988-1989; 20 (Reel 11)
  - Holiday Inn (Acquired by Bass Pic Outside USA), 1989; 21 (Reel 11)
  - Immigration, 1989; 22 (Reel 11)
  - INHILCO H+W Plan, 1982-1989; 23 (Reel 11)
  - INHILCO Negotiations, 1989; 24 (Reel 11)
- D.O. Misc. - '89 Inhilco Research -- '89 Union Busting Master (Reel 12)
  - INILCO Research, 1989; 1 (Reel 12)
  - IUF Corporate Profiles, 1989; 2 (Reel 12)
  - Hard Rock Caf, 3 (Reel 12)
  - IUF Meetings, 1989; 4 (Reel 12)
  - IUF ILO, 1989; 5 (Reel 12)
  - IUF Miscellaneous, 1989; 6 (Reel 12)
  - IUF Nestle, 1989; 7 (Reel 12)
  - IUF Support Letters, 1989; 8 (Reel 12)
  - Morty Miller's Updates, 9 (Reel 12)
  - George Meany Center for Labor Studies, 1989; 10 (Reel 12)
  - Montana, 1989; 11 (Reel 12)
  - NLRB Elections, 1989; 12 (Reel 12)
  - Radisson Plaza LAX, 1989; 13 (Reel 12)
  - Radisson Union Proposals LAX, 1989; 14 (Reel 12)
  - Radisson Campaign (Shearson Mailing 7/89 - 10/89), 1989; 15 (Reel 12)
  - Shop Stewards Training, 1978-1989; 16 (Reel 12)
  - Union Busting Activity, 1989; 17 (Reel 12)
- D.O. Misc. -- '89 Un. Ind. Show CI Ristorante N.Y. -- roll no. 13 Master (Reel 13)
  - Union Industries Show San Jose, CA, 1989; 1 (Reel 13)
  - Clarion Castle Hotel Miami - Local 355, 1989-1990; 2 (Reel 13)
  - CI Ristorante Strike and Contract, 1990; 3 (Reel 13)
  - CI Ristorante "New York City", 4 (Reel 13)
- D.O. Misc. -- CI 101 things to eat Col. Williamsb. Neg. -- roll no. 14 Master (Reel 14)
  - CI 101 Things to Eat, 1 (Reel 14)
  - CW 1990, 2 (Reel 14)
  - Colonial Williamsburg Negotiations - Morty Miller's Notes, 1990-1991; 3 (Reel 14)
- D.O. Misc. -- CW 1990-1991 -- 1990 IUF/NARO -- roll no. 15 Master (Reel 15)
  - CW 1990-1991, 1 (Reel 15)
  - CW 1990-1991, 2 (Reel 15)
  - ARA-Hofstra 1990 Local 100, 3 (Reel 15)
  - Hofstra University, 4 (Reel 15)
  - Hofstra, 5 (Reel 15)
  - Host. 1990, 6 (Reel 15)
  - ILO-IUF, 1990; 7 (Reel 15)
  - IUF-Miscellaneous, 1990; 8 (Reel 15)
  - IUF Nestle's, 1990; 9 (Reel 15)
  - IUF/Naro, 10 (Reel 15)
- Director of Organization Miscellaneous Files -- Art XX Determinations - Food & Beverage Dept. -- roll no. 15-B Master (Reel 16)
  - Article XX Determination, 1982-1983; 1 (Reel 16)
  - AFL-CIO Convention (12/77), 1977; 2 (Reel 16)
  - AFL-CIO Convention Washington D.C., 1979; 3 (Reel 16)
  - Co-Op Organizing Campaign - Kentucky-Ohio, 1979-1984; 4 (Reel 16)
  - Mimeo Letters Organization Department, 1957-1980; 5 (Reel 16)
  - DUU Bradstreet, 1975-1982; 6 (Reel 16)
  - Food and Beverage Department AFL-CIO, 1960-1966; 7 (Reel 16)
- D.O. Misc. -- '90 Jolly Fisherman -- '85-90 Kamper Group -- roll no. 16 - Master (Reel 17)
  - Jolly Fisherman, 1990; 1 (Reel 17)
  - The Kamper Group, 1985-1990; 2 (Reel 17)
- Director of Organization Miscellaneous Files -- Hilton Hotels - Worlds Fair -- roll no. 16-B Master (Reel 18)
  - Hilton Hotels, 1974-1980; 1 (Reel 18)
  - Government Contracts, 2 (Reel 18)
  - Government Wage Deter, 3 (Reel 18)
  - Sambo's, 1975-1983; 4 (Reel 18)
  - Sambo's Special Fund, 1982-1983; 5 (Reel 18)
  - Sheraton Special Fund, 6 (Reel 18)
  - Solidarity Day Enrollment Forms, 1981; 7 (Reel 18)
  - Solidarity Day Reimbursement Bills Paid, 8 (Reel 18)
  - Solidarity Day Correspondence, 1981; 9 (Reel 18)
  - Solidarity Day, 1983; 10 (Reel 18)
  - World's Fair, 1982; 11 (Reel 18)
- D.O. Misc. -- Files - ARA Information Tip Regulation -- roll no. 17B Master (Reel 19)
  - ARA Information, 1 (Reel 19)
  - Canadian Law, 2 (Reel 19)
  - Canadian Labour Congress Disputes, 3 (Reel 19)
  - NBA, 4 (Reel 19)
  - Motion Picture Industry Council, 5 (Reel 19)
  - Local #6 Medical Plan, 6 (Reel 19)
  - Marriot Campaign, 7 (Reel 19)
  - Florida Hotel Motel and Allied Trades Council, 8 (Reel 19)
  - Local 353 Dallas Organization and Texas Subsidy, 9 (Reel 19)
  - Harvey's Original Campaign, 10 (Reel 19)
  - William Kircher Personal File, 11 (Reel 19)
  - AM FAC, 12 (Reel 19)
  - Health Maintenance, 13 (Reel 19)
  - George Meany Labor Studies June 10-15, 1984, 14 (Reel 19)
  - Dun and Bradstreet, 15 (Reel 19)
  - Tefra 8% Tip Tax, 16 (Reel 19)
  - Tip Regulation, 17 (Reel 19)
- D.O. Misc. -- Files -- Director of Orgz. HMO Human Resources Center, Inc. -- roll no. 18B Master (Reel 20)
  - Director of Organization Propaganda File, 1 (Reel 20)
  - Propaganda, 1983-1984; 2 (Reel 20)
  - Pich Americana Hotel, 3 (Reel 20)
  - Playboy, 4 (Reel 20)
  - Poconos, 5 (Reel 20)
  - Campbell Pocono Mountains, 6 (Reel 20)
  - Organizer Survey, 7 (Reel 20)
  - Pacific Amphitheater Ogden, 8 (Reel 20)
  - Union Airline Caterers Contract, 9 (Reel 20)
  - HMO-Human Resources Center Inc., 10 (Reel 20)
- D.O. Misc. -- Files -- Sky Chefs Tavern on the Green -- roll no. 19B Master (Reel 21)
  - Sky Chefs Little Rock 1 Unit, 1 (Reel 21)
  - Cincinnati 1 Unit, 2 (Reel 21)
  - Admirals and Ambassador Club, 3 (Reel 21)
  - Towne House - Rochester, 4 (Reel 21)
  - Flagship - Rochester, 5 (Reel 21)
  - Tulsa Computer Center, 6 (Reel 21)
  - L'Enfant - Washington D.C., 7 (Reel 21)
  - American Hotel - Canyon Resort Palm Spring California, 8 (Reel 21)
  - Rochester - 2 Units, 9 (Reel 21)
  - Rochester Airport, 10 (Reel 21)
  - Little Rock Americana Inn - Little Rock, AK, 11 (Reel 21)
  - President's Council, 12 (Reel 21)
  - St. Louis Airport, 13 (Reel 21)
  - Barkley House, 14 (Reel 21)
  - Flagship Hotel - Local 471 Albany, NY, 15 (Reel 21)
  - Acorn, 16 (Reel 21)
  - Schraffts Master Contract, 17 (Reel 21)
  - Steak and Brew Cattleman's Enrico and Paglieri Inc., 18 (Reel 21)
  - Tia Maria, 19 (Reel 21)
  - Hungry Tiger Restaurants, 20 (Reel 21)
  - Tavern on the Green, 21 (Reel 21)
- D.O. Misc. -- Files -- Bay Meadow Catering Sambo's - roll no. 20B Master (Reel 22)
  - Bay Meadow Catering, 1 (Reel 22)
  - Alaska Pipeline, 1972-1974; 2 (Reel 22)
  - B/G Sandwich, 3 (Reel 22)
  - Maxwell Plum, 4 (Reel 22)
  - Congratulations, 5 (Reel 22)
  - Alaska Pipeline 1975-Present, 6 (Reel 22)
  - Colonade Cafeteria Contracts, 7 (Reel 22)
  - Copper Wheel Restaurants, 8 (Reel 22)
  - Chef's Orchid, 9 (Reel 22)
  - Dutch Inns of America, 10 (Reel 22)
  - Sambo's, 11 (Reel 22)
- D.O. Misc. -- Files -- International Pancake I-HOP 46-50 Bronx -- roll no. 21B Master (Reel 23)
  - International House of Pancakes, 1 (Reel 23)
  - I-HOP #46-6 Touchmont, 2 (Reel 23)
  - I-HOP #46-7 Jackson Heights, 3 (Reel 23)
  - I-HOP West Hempstead, 4 (Reel 23)
  - I-HOP Darien Conn., 5 (Reel 23)
  - I-HOP Valley Stredin, 6 (Reel 23)
  - I-HOP Plainview, 7 (Reel 23)
  - I-HOP Brooklyn, 8 (Reel 23)
  - I-HOP Massapequa, 9 (Reel 23)
  - I-HOP Jamaica, 10 (Reel 23)
  - I-HOP Manhasset, 11 (Reel 23)
  - I-HOP Hartsdale, 12 (Reel 23)
  - I-HOP Flushing, 13 (Reel 23)
  - Bourbon, Orleans Limited, 14 (Reel 23)
  - I-HOP Little Neck, 15 (Reel 23)
  - I-HOP Oceanside, 16 (Reel 23)
  - I-HOP Huntington Station, 17 (Reel 23)
  - I-HOP Bronx, 18 (Reel 23)
  - I-HOP Rosedale, 19 (Reel 23)
  - I-HOP Williston Park, 20 (Reel 23)
  - I-HOP Commade, 21 (Reel 23)
  - I-HOP Flushing, 22 (Reel 23)
  - I-HOP Babylon, 23 (Reel 23)
  - I-HOP Hicksville, 24 (Reel 23)
  - I-HOP Brentwood, 25 (Reel 23)
  - I-HOP Bronx, 26 (Reel 23)
- D.O. Misc. -- Sky Chef-Oklahoma Cty - Sky Chef Sale-Delwre -- roll no. 22B Master (Reel 24)
  - Sky Chefs - Oklahoma City, OK - Arbitration Proceedings, 1987; 1 (Reel 24)
  - Sky Chefs Terminals - Right to Work Laws, 2 (Reel 24)
  - Sky Chefs, 1975; 3 (Reel 24)
  - Sky Chefs Negotiations, 1975; 4 (Reel 24)
  - Sky Chefs - Fringe Benefit Supplements, 1975; 5 (Reel 24)
  - Sky Chefs - Hilo, HI Airport Unit, 1977-1980; 6 (Reel 24)
  - Sky Chefs - Hilo, HI Flight Kitchen, 1981; 7 (Reel 24)
  - Sky Chefs Pleadings Vol. I and II, 1984-1985; 8 (Reel 24)
  - Sky Chefs - Proposals, 1979; 9 (Reel 24)
  - Flagship International Settlement Agreement, 1979; 10 (Reel 24)
  - Inn of 6 Flags, 11 (Reel 24)
  - Sky Chef Miscellaneous, 1985-1986; 12 (Reel 24)
  - Sky Chef Restructure, 1985-1986; 13 (Reel 24)
  - Sky Chef Sale - Delaware North Company, 1986-1987; 14 (Reel 24)
- D.O. Misc. -- Sky Chef Sale -- Sky Chef Grievances -- roll no. 23B Master (Reel 25)
  - Sky Chef Sale Host/Marriott, 1986; 1 (Reel 25)
  - Sky Chef 0 Flight Benefits Legal File, 1986; 2 (Reel 25)
  - Fringe Benefit Supplements, 1978; 3 (Reel 25)
  - Sky Chef Flight Benefits Arbitration, 1985; 4 (Reel 25)
  - Sky Chefs Grievances - Mobile, AL Airport Unit 1986, 5 (Reel 25)
  - Morty Miller's Note Re: Grievance #86-46 Kate Possien - Mob Grievance #86-47 Brenda Dowdle, 6 (Reel 25)
  - Sky Chefs Grievances Phoenix, AZ Flight Kitchen Unit, 1986-1988; 7 (Reel 25)
- D.O. Misc. -- Sky Chef Grievances Concession Air Griev. -- 24B Master (Reel 26)
  - Sky Chefs Grievances Tucson, AZ Flight Kitchen Unit, 1986-1987; 1 (Reel 26)
  - Sky Chefs Grievances - Los Angeles, CA Flight Kitchen Unit, 1986-1988; 2 (Reel 26)
  - Sky Chefs Grievances San Diego, CA Airport Unit, 1987-1988; 3 (Reel 26)
  - Sky Chefs Grievances San Diego, CA Airport Unit, 1986; 4 (Reel 26)
  - Sky Chefs Grievances San Francisco, CA Airport Unit, 1986-1988; 5 (Reel 26)
  - Sky Chefs Grievances Denver, CO Flight Kitchen Unit, 1987; 6 (Reel 26)
  - Sky Chefs Grievances Washington, DC Airport Unit, 1987-1988; 7 (Reel 26)
  - Sky Chefs Grievances Washington, DC Airport Unit, 1987-1988; 8 (Reel 26)
  - Sky Chefs Grievances Miami, FL Airport Unit, 1985; 9 (Reel 26)
  - Sky Chefs Grievances Honolulu, HI Airport Unit, 1986-1988; 10 (Reel 26)
  - Sky Chefs Grievances Chicago, IL Airport Unit, 1987-1988; 11 (Reel 26)
  - Sky Chefs Grievances Boston, MA Airport Unit, 1986-1988; 12 (Reel 26)
  - Morty Miller's Notes Re: Grievance #86-53 Angelo Zirpolo, 13 (Reel 26)